<Dialogue>
	<DialogueNode id="start">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="60">I hope you didn’t climb up here to report the kid, because I’ve got more important duties than hunting down some stolen sweets.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="1">Kid?</Option>
			<Option link="2">Duties?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="1">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="75">You new around here or something? That snot-nosed little kid runs around causing chaos to everyone around here.</Text>
			<Text time="120">If you want someone to do something about it, take it up with the other two guards. They’re always complaining about being bored…</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="1.1">Who are the other Guards?</Option>
			<Option link="2">What are your duties?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="1.1">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="120">Peh, you haven’t talked to the others yet, eh? One on the far side of the town ain’t so bad, but he’s only in it for the fighting. And they say I’m a grump.</Text>
			<Text time="120">The one by the well is just nauseating though. Never shuts up, always befriending the visitors. Really, I’m the only one who does my duties.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="2">What are your duties?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="2">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="120">Sojourn ain’t guarding itself, and heaven knows the others don’t bother watching these walls. Listen, one day, that ol’ Lord of the Moon is coming back, and when he does, someone’s gotta be on the lookout!</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="3">Lord of the Moon?</Option>
			<Option link="4">Sounds exhausting…</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="3">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="120">What? You mean don’t know the legends? I thought everyone knew them! Well, something’s coming, and you best bet we gotta be ready when it does! How everyone else sits by and wastes time like this is beyond me!</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="4">Sounds exhausting…</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="4" flag="SojournGuard_4">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="120">Well, I dunno how to tell you this, but it’s my job. We’re the first line of defense, and if those screwballs don’t like it, then that’s that. And if whatever’s making those monsters disappear comes and kills us all, well then I suppose I can give them an earful that I tried to warn them! Now go away, I’m busy.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
</Dialogue>