<Dialogue>
	<DialogueNode id="start">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="120">Well hey there traveler! What brings you to our little town? Something to report? Your best bet is taking it up with that guy over by the horse.</Text>
			<Text time="60">He’s a bit on the rough side if you ask me, but he’s always looking for action.</Text>
			<Text time="60">Though if you’re looking to chat, I’m all ears!</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="1">Why not you?</Option>
			<Option link="6">About Sojourn?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="1">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="60">Oh well...</Text>
			<Text time="60">You see, I've got a real important job I’m doing right now.</Text>
			<Text time="60">Yup, sorry pal, can’t help you.</Text>
			<Text time="60">Like I said, your best bet is taking it up with that guy.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="2">What’s your job?</Option>
			<Option link="3">That guy?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="2">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="60">Uhm...</Text>
			<Text time="60">I uh...</Text>
			<Text time="60">I’ve gotta watch over this here well!</Text>
			<Text time="90">Ya, you see, it might just look like an ordinary well to our common eyes, but it's actually a magical well.</Text>
			<Text time="75">Yes sir, it's got a mind of its own, and the poor thing gets lonely, so it's my job to keep it company.</Text>
			<Text time="75">If this thing were to get angry, it could end the world as we know it! Ain’t that right, magic well.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="2.1">...</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="2.1">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="60">You couldn’t hear her, but she totally just said yes.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="2.2">Magic Well?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="2.2" flag="SojournGuard3_2.2">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="120">Alright, you caught me red handed. I may have wanted to try my hand at telling a story. Wasn’t that good, was it? Welp, practice makes perfect, and with how many visitors we get, I’ll be having lots of practice.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="3">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="90">Oh yeah, he’s one of my fellow guards, but with how often he leaves to look for some monster to fight, you wouldn’t know it.</Text>
			<Text time="90">I don’t really get him. I mean, we’ve got a nice town here, nice people, a cozy little place. So why go looking for a fight?</Text>
			<Text time="60">Especially when you might just go and poke something best left alone.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="4">Such as?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="4">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="60">You must not have talked to our watchman. There’s a whole lot of freaky things wandering around these parts.</Text>
			<Text time="90">Well, there used to be. Lately, they’ve all but disappeared, and our watchman seems to think some serious beast caused it. Personally, I’m inclined to believe him, monsters don’t just disappear like that.</Text>
			<Text time="60">While I’m glad the monsters are gone, I wouldn’t go around poking a sleeping bear, if you know what I mean.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="5">Beast?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="6">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="75">We’ve got a fine town here I’ll say. Ain’t too big so everybody knows everybody, and we’re in the middle of a nice forest! What’s not to love?</Text>
			<Text time="180">Well, before recently, I’d have warned you about all the monsters that liked to pop in on us, but recently they’ve seemed to stop coming. Our watchman seems to think that some beast is responsible, and if that’s true, then I might just have to go out and thank the guy!</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="5">Beast?</Option>
			<Option link="7">Why become a guard?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="5" flag="SojournGuard3_5">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="60">Oh yeah, he loves talking about all sorts of beasties, always telling us about some freaky thing that’s gonna eat the town or something.</Text>
			<Text time="60">If I’m being honest, I kinda like to hear all the stories he’s got to tell, and I can’t help but respect his dedication to the job.</Text>
			<Text time="90">But hey, don’t tell him I said that! I’m willing to bet it’d all go to his head, and if he knew I respected the hell out of him, then I wouldn’t be able to poke fun at him anymore.</Text>
		</Dialogue>
		<Options>
			<Option link="2.2">Magic Well?</Option>
		</Options>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode id="7">
		<Dialogue>
			<Text time="120">Well… I can’t lie, it's a pretty easy job. I mean, you get paid just to hang around, talk to all the new faces that pop up here, and just gotta fend off the occasional monsters? Sounds like a dream job to me, minus the monster part of course.</Text>
			<Text time="75">Though since they’ve stopped showing up, I guess there might not be as much of a need for guards anymore. Oh no, I might be out of a job soon!</Text>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
</Dialogue>